[left hand] reach toward the middle cup | [right hand] reach toward the middle cup lid
[left hand] hold the middle cup | [right hand] twist and remove the lid
[right hand] place the lid on the table | [left hand] reach toward the leftmost cup
[left hand] hold the leftmost cup | [right hand] remove the lid
[right hand] place the lid on the table | [right hand] reach toward the rightmost cup
[left hand] hold the rightmost cup | [right hand] remove the lid
[right hand] place the lid on the table | [right hand] reach toward the fourth cup
[left hand] hold the fourth cup | [right hand] remove the lid
[right hand] place the lid on the table | [left hand] reach toward the second cup
[left hand] hold the second cup | [right hand] remove the lid
[right hand] place the lid on the table